Guide to the Stephen Vincent Benét and Rosemary Benét Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1887-1962; Series I; 16.18; 35 boxes
  - General Correspondence
    - Damrosch, Walter; Damrosch, Margaret, 1939-1946, undated (Box 7, Folder 305)
    - Dan Golenpaul Associates, 1941, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 306)
    - Dana, John Winchester, 1933, undated (Box 8, Folder 307)
    - Daniel, Robert Woodham, 1939 October 1 (Box 8, Folder 308)
    - Dark, Robert, 1938 April 7 (Box 8, Folder 309)
    - Darroch, Lois, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 310)
    - Dartmouth College. Library, 1939 October 26 (Box 8, Folder 311)
    - Daughtery, Charles M[ichael?], 1932 November 6 (Box 8, Folder 312)
    - Davenport, Basil, 1931-1959, undated (Box 8, Folder 313-314)
    - Davidman, Joy, 1936–1943 (Box 8, Folder 315)
    - Clipping removed from Davidman, Joy, 1943 March 30 (Box 123 (Oversize), Folder 3107)
    - Davidson, Donald, 1928, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 316)
    - Davis, Clyde [Brion?], 1937–1939 (Box 8, Folder 317)
    - Davis, Earle, 1939–1940 (Box 8, Folder 318)
    - Davis, Fitzroy, 1943, undated (Box 8, Folder 319)
    - [Davis?], Julia, 1958-1961, undated (Box 8, Folder 320)
    - Davis, Mary Gould, 1936 June 11 (Box 8, Folder 321)
    - Davis, Rita, 1943-1955, undated (Box 8, Folder 322)
    - Davis, [Wilma?], 1939 March 17 (Box 8, Folder 323)
    - Day, George Parmly, 1942 July 7 (Box 8, Folder 324)
    - Day, Peg, 1941-1947, undated (Box 8, Folder 325)
    - Decision, 1940–1941 (Box 8, Folder 326)
    - DeJong, David C[ornel?], 1941 November 10 (Box 8, Folder 327)
    - De Koven, Anna, 1936 April 15 (Box 8, Folder 328)
    - Del Monte Properties Company, 1940 April 29 (Box 8, Folder 329)
    - Delaney, Robert [Mills?], 1939–1941 (Box 8, Folder 330)
    - Delano, William Adams, 1943 March 15 (Box 8, Folder 331)
    - Delbos, Julius, 1943 April 2 (Box 8, Folder 332)
    - Delineator, 1932–1936 (Box 8, Folder 333)
    - Denison, Harold, 1938 April 16 (Box 8, Folder 334)
    - Denney, Reuel, 1938–1939 (Box 8, Folder 335)
    - Derby, Ethel; Derby, Richard, 1940-1943, undated (Box 8, Folder 336)
    - Derleth, August William, 1948, undated (Box 8, Folder 337)
    - DeVane, William C. (William Clyde), 1933 (Box 8, Folder 338)
    - The Dial, 1918 March 12 (Box 8, Folder 339)
    - Dickinson, Asa Don, undated (Box 8, Folder 340)
    - Dickinson College, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 341)
    - Dickson, Lillian, 1937 March 15 (Box 8, Folder 342)
    - Dieterle, William, 1940–1942 (Box 8, Folder 343)
    - Dilliard, Irving, [?] January 22 (Box 8, Folder 344)
    - Dodd, Mead Company, 1936–1942 (Box 8, Folder 345)
    - Dodge, Louis, 1942 July 1 (Box 8, Folder 346)
    - Dollard, John, 1929 January 23 (Box 8, Folder 347)
    - Donaldson, Norman, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 348)
    - Donner, Jane, 1938–1939 (Box 8, Folder 349)
    - Dos Passos, John, 1943 March 15 (Box 8, Folder 350)
    - Dotter, Charles, 1942-1943, undated (Box 8, Folder 351)
    - Doubleday, Doran & Company, 1926-1953, undated (Box 8, Folder 352-354)
    - Douglas, William, 1928-1958, undated (Box 8, Folder 355)
    - Douglas Gibbons Company, 1937–1939 (Box 8, Folder 356)
    - Douglass College, 1937 February 18 (Box 8, Folder 357)
    - Dowdey, Clifford, 1937-1939, undated (Box 8, Folder 358)
    - Dramatists Play Service (New York, N.Y.), 1937–1942 (Box 8, Folder 359)
    - Draper, Ruth, 1955, undated (Box 8, Folder 360)
    - Drew, Fraser Bragg, 1950, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 361)
    - Drummond, Andrew Landale, 1938 March 25 (Box 8, Folder 362)
    - Duncan, Thomas W. (Thomas William), 1936 June 28 (Box 8, Folder 363)
    - Duncombe, Frances, 1943, undated (Box 9, Folder 364)
    - Dunn, Alan, 1956 November 3 (Box 9, Folder 365)
    - Durant, Helen, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 366)
    - Duttons, Inc., 1938, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 367)
    - "E" general, 1915-1962, undated (Box 9, Folder 368-369)
    - E. P. Dutton (Firm), 1951 August 13 (Box 9, Folder 370)
    - Editions for the Armed Services, Inc., 1948 January 26 (Box 9, Folder 371)
    - Edward MacDowell Association, 1935-1952, undated (Box 9, Folder 372)
    - Ehle, John, 1959 February 28 (Box 9, Folder 373)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Dwight David), 1956–1957 (Box 9, Folder 374)
    - Elizabethan Club (Yale University), 1917, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 375)
    - Ellis, Richard, 1945 February 19 (Box 9, Folder 376)
    - Ellsworth, William W[ebster?], 1928–1929 (Box 9, Folder 377)
    - Engle, Paul, 1928-1961, undated (Box 9, Folder 378-381)
    - Clippings removed from Engle, Paul, 1934, 1961 (Box 123 (Oversize), Folder 3108)
    - English, Granville, 1939, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 382)
    - English Folk Dance and Song Society, 1939 April 5 (Box 9, Folder 383)
    - English Folk Dance Society, undated (Box 9, Folder 384)
    - English-Speaking Union of the United States, 1942, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 385)
    - Enoch Pratt Free Library, 1956 April 5 (Box 9, Folder 386)
    - Erasmus Hall, 1937 May 3 (Box 9, Folder 387)
    - Ernst, Morris L[eopold?], 1943 February 8 (Box 9, Folder 388)
    - Erskine, John, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 389)
    - Everts, Effingham, 1920-1943, undated (Box 9, Folder 390-391)
    - "F" general, [circa 1910]-1950, undated (Box 9, Folder 392-393)
    - Fackenthal, Frank Diehl, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 394)
    - Fadiman, Clifton, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 394a)
    - Fadiman, William, 1940 June 24 (Box 9, Folder 395)
    - Fairbanks, Douglas, 1930 February 7 (Box 9, Folder 396)
    - Farr, Hollon A., 1918 February 18 (Box 9, Folder 397)
    - Farrar & Rinehart, 1917–1932 (Box 9, Folder 398)
    - Farrar & Rinehart, 1932-1962, undated (Box 10, Folder 399-409)
    - Farrar, Straus, and Cudahy, 1946–1961 (Box 10, Folder 410)
    - Farrell, James T. (James Thomas), 1942–1943 (Box 10, Folder 411)
    - [Favard?], Beatrix, 1938, undated (Box 10, Folder 412)
    - Favard, Bertha des Combes, 1927–1946 (Box 10, Folder 413)
    - Fenton, Charles A., 1952–1957 (Box 10, Folder 414-415)
    - Fenton, Charles A., 1957-1960, undated (Box 11, Folder 416-417)
    - Ferber, Edna, 1935 June 18 (Box 11, Folder 418)
    - Fergus, Phyllis, 1934, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 419)
    - Ferguson, Milton James, 1937 May 6 (Box 11, Folder 420)
    - Ferril, Thomas Hornsby, 1935 January 21 (Box 11, Folder 421)
    - Ficke, Arthur Davison, 1928, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 422)
    - Field, Rachel, 1935, undated (Box 11, Folder 423)
    - Filler, Louis, 1962 January 30 (Box 11, Folder 424)
    - Fillmore, Parker, 1943 March 14 (Box 11, Folder 425)
    - Finch College, 1937–1953 (Box 11, Folder 426)
    - Finkelstein, Louis, 1941, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 427)
    - Fischer, Marjorie, 1941 January 15 (Box 11, Folder 428)
    - Fish, Williston, 1928 December 18 (Box 11, Folder 429)
    - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield, 193[?]-1956, undated (Box 11, Folder 430)
    - Fisher, Irving, 1943 March 14 (Box 11, Folder 431)
    - Fitzgerald, Robert, 1935 May 11 (Box 11, Folder 432)
    - Flaccus, Kimball, 1938 May 4 (Box 11, Folder 433)
    - Flack, Frank, 1943–1944 (Box 11, Folder 434)
    - Flandrau, Grace, undated (Box 11, Folder 434a)
    - Fletcher, John Gould, 1937, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 435)
    - Foerster, Norman, 1932-1943, undated (Box 11, Folder 436)
    - Follensbee, Oliver, 1934–1947 (Box 11, Folder 437)
    - Ford, Charles Henri, 1935, undated (Box 11, Folder 438)
    - Foreign Affairs, 1935, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 439)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1945 March 30 (Box 11, Folder 440)
    - Fortune, 1932–1946 (Box 11, Folder 441)
    - The Forum, 1927–1937 (Box 11, Folder 442)
    - Foster, Reginald C., 1940 April 8 (Box 11, Folder 443)
    - Fowler, Albert Vann, 1938 February 12 (Box 11, Folder 444)
    - France, Henry, 1931-1950, undated (Box 11, Folder 445)
    - Frank, Josette, 1943 March 15 (Box 11, Folder 446)
    - Franken, Rose, 1943 March 13 (Box 11, Folder 447)
    - Frankenberg, Lloyd, 1939–1940 (Box 11, Folder 448)
    - Freedom House (U.S.), 1942 (Box 11, Folder 449)
    - Freeman, Douglas Southall, 1933–1942 (Box 11, Folder 450)
    - Freeman, Joseph, 1943 March 13 (Box 11, Folder 451)
    - French, Sidney J. (Sidney James), Mrs., 1936 January 11 (Box 11, Folder 452)
    - "French Letters", 1920-1951, undated (Box 11, Folder 453-454)
    - Friends of Democracy (U.S.), 1943 February 10 (Box 11, Folder 455)
    - Friends of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade, 1938–1939 (Box 11, Folder 456)
    - Friends of the Middle Border, 1943 June 22 (Box 11, Folder 457)
    - Frost, F. H. (Frederick Hazard), 1943 March 11 (Box 11, Folder 458)
    - Fuess, Claude Moore, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 459)
    - Fuller, Jane, undated (Box 11, Folder 460)
    - Fuller, Margaret, 1928 November 14 (Box 11, Folder 461)
    - Fuller, Muriel, 1937 March 8 (Box 11, Folder 462)
    - Funk, Rey Leland, 1911–1913 (Box 11, Folder 463)
    - "G" general, 1921-1954, undated (Box 11, Folder 464-467)
    - G. P. Putnam's Sons, 1953 April 15 (Box 12, Folder 468)
    - Gammell, Helena Hope, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 469)
    - Gannett, Lewis, 1933–1960 (Box 12, Folder 470)
    - Gannon, Michael, 1938 December 18 (Box 12, Folder 471)
    - George H. Doran Company, 1923, 1925 (Box 12, Folder 472)
    - Empty folder (Box 12, Folder 473)
    - George School (Bucks County, Pa.), 1938 January 3 (Box 12, Folder 474)
    - Georgia State Library, 1946 May 2 (Box 12, Folder 475)
    - Gephart, Besse Patterson, 1933-1946, undated (Box 12, Folder 476)
    - German American Writers Association, 1939–1940 (Box 12, Folder 477)
    - Gessner, Robert, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 478)
    - Getchell, Everett Lamont, 1942 February 11 (Box 12, Folder 479)
    - Gilbert, Paul T., 1940-1943, undated (Box 12, Folder 480)
    - Gill, Brendan, undated (Box 12, Folder 481)
    - Gillispie, Abraham Lincoln, 1943 March 15 (Box 12, Folder 482)
    - Gish, Lillian, undated (Box 12, Folder 483)
    - Glasgow, Ellen [Anderson Gholson?], 1930–1942 (Box 12, Folder 484)
    - Gleason, George Scott, 1928 October 30 (Box 12, Folder 485)
    - Glossbrenner, Edna [Schnell?], 1943, undated (Box 12, Folder 486)
    - Goldsmith, Wallace, 1937 November 17 (Box 12, Folder 487)
    - Good Housekeeping, 1938 December 19 (Box 12, Folder 488)
    - Gordon, J. King, 1943 April 19 (Box 12, Folder 489)
    - Grainger, Boyne, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 490)
    - Grant, Robert, 1933, undated (Box 12, Folder 491)
    - Gray, Charles Wright, 1925 June 1 (Box 12, Folder 492)
    - Greene, Henry Coply; Greene, Rosalind, 1944-1946, undated (Box 12, Folder 493)
    - Greene, Richard L[eighton?], 1940 May 27 (Box 12, Folder 494)
    - Greenwich Academy (Greenwich, Conn.), 1950 January 4 (Box 12, Folder 495)
    - Gregory, Paul, 1955-1959, undated (Box 12, Folder 496)
    - Griffis, Elliot, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 497)
    - Grimes, Nadine Hall, 1923-1944, undated (Box 12, Folder 498)
    - [Griswold], Mary, 1959–1960 (Box 12, Folder 499)
    - Grolier Club, [?] September 30 (Box 12, Folder 500)
    - Groves, John Stuart, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 501)
    - Gruenberg, Sidonie Matsner, 1943 March 16 (Box 12, Folder 502)
    - Guaranty Trust Company of New York, 1927–1941 (Box 12, Folder 503)
    - Gunther, John; Gunther, Frances, 1938–1948 (Box 12, Folder 504)
    - "H" general, 1907-1961, undated (Box 12, Folder 505-509)
    - H. W. Wilson Company, 1939 April 27 (Box 12, Folder 510)
    - Hagedorn, Hermann, 1938, undated (Box 12, Folder 511)
    - Hahn, Emily, 1958, undated (Box 12, Folder 512)
    - Hahn, Mannel, 1939 September 21 (Box 12, Folder 513)
    - Hale, Barbara, 1945-1948, undated (Box 12, Folder 514)
    - Hale, Nancy, 1958, undated (Box 12, Folder 515)
    - Hale, Richard W., 1936 December 28 (Box 12, Folder 516)
    - Hale, Richard Walden, [?] May 26 (Box 13, Folder 517)
    - Halifax, Charles Lindley Wood, Viscount, 1941 November 10 (Box 13, Folder 518)
    - Hall, Emma Swan, 1941 April 29 (Box 13, Folder 519)
    - Halle Bros. Co., 1923 (Box 13, Folder 520)
    - Halter, Ernst J., 1948 May 10 (Box 13, Folder 521)
    - Hambleton, T. Edward, 1940 January 4 (Box 13, Folder 522)
    - Hamill, Marjorie, undated (Box 13, Folder 523)
    - [Hamish Hamilton, Ltd.?], undated (Box 13, Folder 524)
    - Hand, Learned; Hand, Frances, 1943-1948, undated (Box 13, Folder 525)
    - Hanson, Philip, 1961, undated (Box 13, Folder 526)
    - Harcourt, Brace and Company, 1939, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 527)
    - Hard, Walter [R.?], 1940, undated (Box 13, Folder 528)
    - Harlan, Ethel; Harlan, John, 1924-1962, undated (Box 13, Folder 529-531)
    - Harper Brothers, 1939–1958 (Box 13, Folder 532)
    - Harper's Bazaar, 1932-1935, undated (Box 13, Folder 533)
    - Harriman, Margaret Case, 1944 October 26 (Box 13, Folder 534)
    - Harriman, W. Averell (William Averell), 1952 December 26 (Box 13, Folder 535)
    - Harris, Cyril, [?] August 29 (Box 13, Folder 536)
    - Harris, Mildred VerSoy, 1953 August 1 (Box 13, Folder 537)
    - Hatch, Richard Warren, 1937 July 17 (Box 13, Folder 538)
    - Hatfield, Lansing, 1939 May 18 (Box 13, Folder 539)
    - Hauser, Jacob, 1935 July 5 (Box 13, Folder 540)
    - Havens, Lorraine, 1938 April 6 (Box 13, Folder 541)
    - Hayes, Caryl May, 1930 May 29 (Box 13, Folder 542)
    - Hayes, Dorsha, 1943 March 18 (Box 13, Folder 543)
    - Hayes, H. Gordon (Harry Gordon), 1929 March 21 (Box 13, Folder 544)
    - Hays, Elinor [Rice?], 1943 March 23 (Box 13, Folder 545)
    - Hazard, Thomas Pierrepont; Hazard, Nancy, 1931-1943, undated (Box 13, Folder 546-547)
    - Hazard family, 1933-1943, undated (Box 13, Folder 548)
    - Heely, Allen; Heely, Henriette, 1939-1942, undated (Box 13, Folder 549)
    - Heibron, Adelaide, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 550)
    - Heinemann (Firm), 1926 (Box 13, Folder 551)
    - Hendricks, Grace, undated (Box 13, Folder 552)
    - Henning, Basil [Duke], 1939 October 31 (Box 13, Folder 553)
    - Henry, Françoise, 1929-1952, undated (Box 13, Folder 554-558)
    - Henry Holt and Company, 1920-1943, undated (Box 14, Folder 559-560)
    - Hepburn, Elizabeth Newport, 1937, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 561)
    - Hepburn, Katharine, 1941-1943, undated (Box 14, Folder 562)
    - Heyward, DuBose; Heyward, Dorothy, 1931-1943, undated (Box 14, Folder 563)
    - Hicks, Helen Gertrude, 1939–1940 (Box 14, Folder 564)
    - Hill, Carol, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 565)
    - Hill, Frederick Trevor, 1929 March 8 (Box 14, Folder 566)
    - Hillyer, Robert, 1940–1941 (Box 14, Folder 567)
    - Hogan C[harles] B[eecher], 1940 January 25 (Box 14, Folder 568)
    - Holland, Cecil Fletcher, 1943 April 7 (Box 14, Folder 569)
    - Holmes, John, 1934-1955, undated (Box 14, Folder 570)
    - Holmes, Ruth, undated (Box 14, Folder 571)
    - Hopkins, Catharine, 1923-1924, undated (Box 14, Folder 572)
    - Hopkins, Lydia, 1925 (Box 14, Folder 573)
    - Hopper, Frances, 1935, undated (Box 14, Folder 574)
    - Hoppin, Frederick Street, 1943, undated (Box 14, Folder 575)
    - Horch, Franz, 1941 November 26 (Box 14, Folder 576)
    - Horn, Stanley F., 1935 March 8 (Box 14, Folder 577)
    - Hough, Frank O. (Frank Olney), 1941 May 6 (Box 14, Folder 578)
    - Houghton, Norris, 1962 January 1 (Box 14, Folder 579)
    - Houghton Mifflin and Company, 1941, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 580)
    - House & Garden, 1942, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 581)
    - Howard, Sidney Coe; Howard, Polly, 1933-1940, undated (Box 14, Folder 582)
    - Howe, M. A. De Wolfe (Mark Anthony De Wolfe), 1935–1937 (Box 14, Folder 583)
    - Howe, Mark De Wolfe, 1933 November 3 (Box 14, Folder 584)
    - Howell, Soskin, Publishers, 1940 February 21 (Box 14, Folder 585)
    - Hoyt, Nancy, [?] May 2 (Box 14, Folder 586)
    - Hughes, Langston
    - Hughes, Rupert, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 587)
    - Hull, Helen [R. (Helen Rose)?], 1939 April 25 (Box 14, Folder 588)
    - Hume, Cyril, 1923–1943 (Box 14, Folder 589)
    - Hunter College, 1936 March 22 (Box 14, Folder 590)
    - Hutchins, Robert Maynard, 1938 May 23 (Box 14, Folder 591)
    - "I" general, 1932–1942 (Box 14, Folder 592)
    - Illinois State Historical Society, 1953 July 22 (Box 14, Folder 593)
    - Infantry Journal, 1942–1943 (Box 14, Folder 594)
    - Ingalls, Jeremy, 1941–1949 (Box 14, Folder 595)
    - Institute of American Genealogy, 1938 February 5 (Box 14, Folder 596)
    - Institute of Current Literature, 1928 November 5 (Box 14, Folder 597)
    - Institute of Early American History Culture (Williamsburg, Va.), 1955 March 4 (Box 14, Folder 598)
    - Iowa State College, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 599)
    - Irwin, Will, [?] March 10 (Box 14, Folder 600)
    - Isaacs, Stanley M. (Stanley Myer), 1936 October 20 (Box 14, Folder 601)
    - Iselin, [?], 1933, undated (Box 14, Folder 602)
    - Ivens, Joris, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 603)
    - "J" general, 1926-1960, undated (Box 14, Folder 604-605)
    - J. B. Lippincott Co., 1938 March 1 (Box 14, Folder 606)
    - J. Walter Thompson Company, 1928 August 15 (Box 14, Folder 607)
    - Jack, Theodore Henley, 1946 April 24 (Box 14, Folder 608)
    - Jackson, Ely[?], 1934, undated (Box 14, Folder 609)
    - Jackson, Katherine Gauss, 1940, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 610)
    - Jackson, Stuart W. (Stuart Wells), 1934-1943, undated (Box 15, Folder 611)
    - Jacob, Heinrich Eduard, 1949 November 24 (Box 15, Folder 612)
    - James, Philip, 1940–1941 (Box 15, Folder 613)
    - James Weldon Johnson Literary Guild, 1943 March 15 (Box 15, Folder 614)
    - Jennings, Oliver [Gould?], 1943, undated (Box 15, Folder 615)
    - Jessup, [Philip C. (Philip Caryl)?], 1943 March 15 (Box 15, Folder 616)
    - Jewett, Arno Joseph, 1953 June 8 (Box 15, Folder 617)
    - Jewish Theological Seminary of America, 1949 November 15 (Box 15, Folder 618)
    - John Day Company, 1934 March 2 (Box 15, Folder 619)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1925-1958, undated (Box 15, Folder 620)
    - Johnson, Grace Nail, 1943 March 13 (Box 15, Folder 621)
    - Jonathan Edwards College (Yale University), 1939 April 18 (Box 15, Folder 622)
    - Jones, Andrew (cousin), 1932-1937, undated (Box 15, Folder 623-632)
    - Jones, Andrew (cousin), 1938-1958, undated (Box 16, Folder 633-637)
    - Jones, Mary Cadwalader, [?] November 17 (Box 16, Folder 638)
    - Jones, [Richelieu?], 1935–1942 (Box 16, Folder 639)
    - Jones, Robert Edmond, 1938, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 640)
    - Jones, Warring, [?] November 20 (Box 16, Folder 641)
    - Joyce, Alice, 1945 May 16 (Box 16, Folder 642)
    - The Junior Fortnightly, 1932-1950, undated (Box 16, Folder 643-645)
    - Junior League of the City of New York, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 646)
    - "K" general, 1919-1960, undated (Box 16, Folder 647-648)
    - Kansas State Teachers College of Emporia, 1943 January 14 (Box 16, Folder 649)
    - Kantor, MacKinlay, 1934-1943, undated (Box 16, Folder 650)
    - Printed card removed from Kantor, MacKinlay, undated (Box 123 (Oversize), Folder 3109)
    - Kates, George N. (George Norbert), [1928?] December 27 (Box 16, Folder 651)
    - Kaufman, Paul, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 652)
    - Kaup, Elzabeth Dewing, 1920, undated (Box 16, Folder 653)
    - [Kearny Thomas?], 1940 April 21 (Box 16, Folder 654)
    - Kebbon, Eric, 1943 March 14 (Box 16, Folder 655)
    - Kennedy, Foster, 1940, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 656)
    - Kennedy, Katherine, 1953 February 16 (Box 16, Folder 657)
    - Kent, Elizabeth E[aton?], 1938–1939 (Box 16, Folder 658)
    - Kent, Rockwell, 1939 January 13 (Box 16, Folder 659)
    - Kerlan, Irvin, 1947 December 29 (Box 16, Folder 660)
    - Kerr, Elizabeth Margaret, 1941–1942 (Box 16, Folder 661)
    - Kibbee, Roland, [?] July 6 (Box 16, Folder 662)
    - Kimbrough, Emily, 1934-1949, undated (Box 16, Folder 663)
    - King, Edith, 1938-1950, undated (Box 17, Folder 664)
    - King, Marion, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 665)
    - Kingsolving, Sally Bruce, 1929–1931 (Box 17, Folder 666)
    - [Kirby, George H. (George Hughes)?], undated (Box 17, Folder 667)
    - Kleeman, Rita Halle, 1943 October 12 (Box 17, Folder 668)
    - Klemm, Gustav, 1939 August 3 (Box 17, Folder 669)
    - Klumph, Helen, undated (Box 17, Folder 670)
    - Knollenberg, Bernhard, 1940 December 4 (Box 17, Folder 671)
    - Knopf, Blanche W., 1943 March 14 (Box 17, Folder 672)
    - Koch, Frederick H. (Frederick Henry), 1939 July 6 (Box 17, Folder 673)
    - Komroff, Manuel, 1943 March 14 (Box 17, Folder 674)
    - Konkle, Burton Alva, 1938 September 14 (Box 17, Folder 675)
    - Krause, Herbert, 1937–1939 (Box 17, Folder 676)
    - Krents, Milton E., 1943 March 16 (Box 17, Folder 677)
    - Kronovet, Milton, 1938 November 11 (Box 17, Folder 678)
    - Kubie, Lawrence S. (Lawrence Schlesinger), 1943, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 679)
    - Kubik, Gail, 1938 August 20 (Box 17, Folder 680)
    - Kuhn, Irene, 1943 March 15 (Box 17, Folder 681)
    - "L" general, 1928-1962, undated (Box 17, Folder 682-684)
    - The Ladies' Home Journal, 1927–1929 (Box 17, Folder 685)
    - La Farge, Christopher, 1934-1954, undated (Box 17, Folder 686-687)
    - La Farge, Florence, 1933, undated (Box 17, Folder 688)
    - La Farge, Oliver; La Farge, Wanden, 1932-1943, undated (Box 17, Folder 689)
    - Lafayette College (Easton, Pa.), 1928 November 9 (Box 17, Folder 690)
    - Laing, Alexander, 1934 January 17 (Box 17, Folder 691)
    - Lamar, Eugenia Dorothy Blount, 1928 December 17 (Box 17, Folder 692)
    - Lamb, Charles R. (Charles Rollinson), undated (Box 17, Folder 693)
    - Lamb, Lomax, [?] September 12 (Box 17, Folder 694)
    - Lamont, Florence, 1935-1949, undated (Box 17, Folder 695)
    - Lamont, Jean, undated (Box 17, Folder 696)
    - Lane, Jessie A., [?] August 11 (Box 17, Folder 697)
    - Lane, Rose Wilder, 1938 January 27 (Box 17, Folder 698)
    - Laski, Harold Joseph, 1938 October 15 (Box 17, Folder 699)
    - Laughton, Charles, 1952 August 15 (Box 17, Folder 700)
    - Laurence, Dan H., 1950 June 14 (Box 17, Folder 701)
    - Lawrence, Josephine, 1942–1943 (Box 17, Folder 702)
    - Lawrence, Muriel, [?] November 7 (Box 17, Folder 703)
    - Lawson, Katherine Swan, 1937, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 704)
    - Leach, Agnes [Lisle Brown?], 1938-1943, undated (Box 17, Folder 705)
    - League of American Writers, 1937–1940 (Box 17, Folder 706)
    - League of Composers, 1939 January 20 (Box 17, Folder 707)
    - League to Support Poetry (New York, N.Y.), 1939 January 2 (Box 17, Folder 708)
    - Leary, Cornelia, [?] September 23 (Box 17, Folder 709)
    - Ledyard, Isabel, undated (Box 17, Folder 710)
    - Lee, Eleanor, 1943 March 16 (Box 17, Folder 711)
    - Lee, Helen Joy, 1939 May 9 (Box 17, Folder 712)
    - Lee, Muna, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 713)
    - Léon, Maurice, 1943 March 21 (Box 17, Folder 714)
    - Lepper, John Heron, 1934 March 25 (Box 17, Folder 715)
    - Lewis, Dearing, 1949-1953, undated (Box 17, Folder 716)
    - Lewis, Duffy; Lewis, Carol, 1920-1943, undated (Box 17, Folder 717)
    - Clippings removed from Lewis, Duffy; Lewis, Carol, undated (Box 123 (Oversize), Folder 3110)
    - Lewis, Grace Hegger, 1943-1953, undated (Box 18, Folder 718)
    - Lewis, H. H., 1937-1939, undated (Box 18, Folder 719)
    - Lewis, Sinclair, 1941, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 720)
    - Lewis, W. S. (Wilmarth Sheldon); Lewis, Annie, 1928-1961, undated (Box 18, Folder 721)
    - Liberty, 1934 September 10 (Box 18, Folder 722)
    - Library of Congress, 1941-1961, undated (Box 18, Folder 723)
    - Life, 1941–1944 (Box 18, Folder 724)
    - Lile, William Minor, 1929 January 29 (Box 18, Folder 725)
    - Lillard, Richard G[ordon?], 1938 October 21 (Box 18, Folder 726)
    - Lindbergh, Anne Morrow, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 727)
    - Lindquist, Marie, 1941 March 15 (Box 18, Folder 728)
    - Little, Brown and Company, 1947 October 16 (Box 18, Folder 729)
    - Litvak, Anatole, 1942 June 15 (Box 18, Folder 730)
    - Locke, Florence, 1934, 1941 (Box 18, Folder 731)
    - Logan, Joshua; Logan, Nedda, 1948-1962, undated (Box 18, Folder 732)
    - Lohmann, Carl A. (Carl Albert); Lohmann, Helen, 1938, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 733)
    - Lombard, Norman, 1940 February 10 (Box 18, Folder 734)